# **Chris Heibel**

Full Stack Engineer

## Profile

I'm a full stack engineer that thrives under pressure and have worked in many different fields from ski lodges to security and demolition. Those experiences made me realize that I wanted to make a career doing something I enjoy, building things.

# Experience

**General Assembly Software Engineering Immersive, Denver, CO** June 2020 — September 2020

- Immersive Engineering program with 500+ hours of full stack experience.
- Worked on teams of 3-4 to develop React applications.
- Completed 4 projects in allotted time frame.
- Collaborated with other team members on projects and research.

# Projects

- Sick Spots, an application to guide you to new locations where you can ski, mountain bike, or just all around get out and enjoy yourself [React.js, JavaScript, Django, Python, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap]
- DevSpot, a social media applications for developers [React.js, Mongoose, Express, MongoDB, JavaScript, Bootstrap]
- Peaks, an application to log peaks summited, and view others peaks [Mongoose, Express, JavaScript, HTML/CSS]

# Employment History

**Demolition at KCC concrete cutting, Wellington New Zealand**October 2019 — January 2020

Bouncer at WPS Security, Wanaka New Zealand

June 2019 — October 2020

Bouncer at Allied Security, Queenstown New Zealand

April 2019 — June 2019

Driver and Guest Services at Stoked Niseko, Niseko, Hokkaido, Japan December 2018 — March 2019

Produce Clerk at Ridley's Family Market, Laramie, Wyoming

May 2017 — September 2018

### Education

**Economics, University of Wyoming** 

2016 - 2018

4 semesters

#### **Details**

Denver, 80204, USA, 719-225-6136 chrisheibel7@gmail.com

#### Links

Github(github.com/lss555)
Linkedin(linkedin.com/in/chrisheibel7)
Portfolio (lss555.github.io)

### **Skills**

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

MongoDB

Mongoose

**j**Query

React

GitHub

RESTful API's

Grunt

**Express** 

PostgreSQL

Node.js

SASS

Bootstrap

### **Hobbies**

Skiing Gaming

Travel